[{"Pokedex" : "06","Pokemon" : "Charizard","Movie Scene" : "1","Question" : "What does Charizard sometimes do unintentionally?","Answer" : "Set forest fires","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "07","Pokemon" : "Squirtle","Movie Scene" : "1","Question" : "How does Squirtle slow down its enemy?","Answer" : "The bubble technique","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "08","Pokemon" : "Wartortle","Movie Scene" : "1","Question" : "Where does Wartortle hide when hunting prey?","Answer" : "In the water","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "14","Pokemon" : "Kakuna","Movie Scene" : "1","Question" : "How does Kakuna protect itself?","Answer" : "The shell hardens","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "17","Pokemon" : "Pidgeotto","Movie Scene" : "2","Question" : "At what level does Pidgeotto evolve from Pidgey?","Answer" : "Level 36","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "23","Pokemon" : "Ekans","Movie Scene" : "2","Question" : "What does Ekans eat?","Answer" : "The eggs of birds","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "35","Pokemon" : "Clefairy","Movie Scene" : "3","Question" : "What do some people believe about Clefairy?","Answer" : "It prays to the moon","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "49","Pokemon" : "Venomoth","Movie Scene" : "4","Question" : "What part of Venomoth's body is color coded?","Answer" : "The scales on its wings","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "69","Pokemon" : "Bellsprout","Movie Scene" : "5","Question" : "What type of plant does Bellsprout resemble?","Answer" : "Venus flytrap","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "71","Pokemon" : "Victreebel","Movie Scene" : "5","Question" : "Where does Victreebel live?","Answer" : "In huge colonies in the jungle","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "86","Pokemon" : "Seel","Movie Scene" : "6","Question" : "Where does Seel live?","Answer" : "In the arctic","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "88","Pokemon" : "Grimer","Movie Scene" : "6","Question" : "What are the two things Grimer loves?","Answer" : "Dirt and slime","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "96","Pokemon" : "Drowzee","Movie Scene" : "7","Question" : "What gives Drowzee energy?","Answer" : "Sweet dreams from victims","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "98","Pokemon" : "Krabby","Movie Scene" : "7","Question" : "What does Krabby use it pincers for?","Answer" : "Balancing walking and weapons","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "106","Pokemon" : "Hitmonlee","Movie Scene" : "8","Question" : "What body part does Hitmonlee depend on in battle?","Answer" : "Its feet","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "115","Pokemon" : "Kangaskhan","Movie Scene" : "8","Question" : "What does Kangaskhan always take into battle?","Answer" : "Its infant","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "116","Pokemon" : "Horsea","Movie Scene" : "8","Question" : "What does Horsea shoot at bugs?","Answer" : "Blasts of ink","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "131","Pokemon" : "Lapras","Movie Scene" : "9","Question" : "What is sad about Lapras?","Answer" : "They have been over-hunted almost to extinction","Price" : ""},{"Pokedex" : "151","Pokemon" : "Mew","Movie Scene" : "10","Question" : "Why is Mew considered a mirage?","Answer" : "BEcause few people have seen it","Price" : ""}]